(Sheldon:)You see a dragon.
(Howard:)Really?
So we're playing Dungeons and Dragons.
(Howard:)And we walk into a dungeon
and see a dragon?
- lsn't that a Iittle on the nose?
- When you play Chutes and Ladders...
(Sheldon:)...do you complain about all the chutes
and the ladders?
(Leonard:)Are you gonna eat that whole pie?
(Raj:)Maybe. Why not?
Who do I have in my Iife
to watch my figure for?
(Leonard:)Oh, God,
did you watch Bridget Jones again?
(Raj:)No, it's just that
everybody's got someone.
(Raj:)Sheldon's with Amy,
Howard's getting married...
(Raj:)- ...you're dating my sister.
- Now that Howard's getting married...
(Leonard:)...maybe he'll inflate
one of his old girIfriends for you, heh.
(Raj:)You know who I blame
for my loneliness?
(Raj:)The United States of America.
(Raj:)Your movies and your TV shows...
(Raj:)...promised streets paved with beautiful
blonde women with big bazongas.
(Howard:)Eat another pie,
you'll have your own bazongas.
(Raj:)That's cruel.
You know it goes straight to my hips.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, please focus.
(Sheldon:)- You're facing a fire-breathing dragon.
- Unh, I don't know if I wanna play anymore.
Because you don't have a girIfriend?
If that becomes a reason...
(Sheldon:)...not to play Dungeons and Dragons,
this game's in serious trouble.